

# Cory Swanson

Programming & Design

303.709.4337 | cory.swanson1@gmail.com coryswanson.net | linkedin.com/in/cory-swanson

# **AFFILIATION**

#### **COLORADO EVANS SCHOLARS**

I was awarded a Chick Evans Caddie Scholarship to attend CU for four years on a full room-board-tuition scholarship. The requirements to become an Evans Scholar involve having an outstanding caddie record, excellent academics, demonstrated financial need, and outstanding character.

# **SKILLS**

## **ADOBE**

I have exceptional skills in the Adobe suite. Not only in **Illustrator** and **Photoshop**, but also programs like **Acrobat**, Indesign, Dreamweaver, and Lightroom.

#### **WEB DEVELOPMENT**

I have a good handle on the basics of **HTML**, **CSS**, and Command-line **Git**. I am passionate about learning harder concepts like JavaScript and related frameworks, PHP and SQL.

I'm a quick learner and diligent worker whether alone or in a group.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **BOULDER COUNTRY CLUB**

# GOLF CADDIE • MAY 2011 - JULY 2014

Ensured a bright and rewarding round of golf for members. Paced yardages, read greens, advised club selection, and carried members' bags while maintaining a lively mood.

## **MEMBER SERVICES • APRIL 2015 - MAY 2016**

Greeted every member as they arrived. Was responsible for replacing range balls, tidying the immediate grounds, and being knowledgeable about events happening at the club.

# **BENT SPOKE DESIGNS**

# **SOLE PROPRIETOR • NOVEMBER 2016 - MAY 2018**

Forming logos for local startups, student groups at the University of Colorado, and the Colorado Evans Scholars.

## **EDUCATION**

# **UNIVERSITY OF COLORADO, BOULDER**

# **BS-FINANCE • MAY 2018**

Overall GPA: 3.0 Business GPA: 3.0

Neglecting to choose an emphasis within finance, I opted for a mix of investment management and personal finance.

# **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

## **COMMUNITY CYCLES**

# **BICYCLE MECHANIC • MAY 2012 - JULY 2015**

Assisted customers with repairs, purchases, questions regarding how to fix bicycle components. Completely disassembled bikes to be used for parts and recycled what couldn't be used. Hand built showroom bikes to be sold from spare parts.

#### **JIBERISH MENSWEAR**

# **WAREHOUSING • NOVEMBER 2016 - JANUARY 2017**

Packed and shipped Black Friday and Cyber Monday orders. Reorganized the entire warehouse in an ergonomic way. Double checked orders to ensure minimal wrong-item returns. Packed and moved all warehouse contents to a larger storage facility.